CJ ENM presents
a CLIMAX STUDIO production
in association with CJ ENM
STUDIO DRAGON KEYEAST
Executive Producer Jinnie CHOI
Financing Executive LIM Ji Young
Produced by BYUN Seung Min
What...
This isn't working either. Great!
Producer HAN Dong Hwan
Written by YEON Sang Ho
(Based on drama: The Cursed)
Crap. Is it debt collectors?
Shit!
Oh my God, what's this?
Hello, what's your emergency?
Hello?
Can you hear me?
The suspect climbed up the gas pipe.
What about the cause of death
or the weapon?
Well...
The victim's autopsy showed
a huge amount of PSP toxins.
Paralytic shellfish poisoning?
Yes, it's the deadliest
toxin found in shellfish,
similar to fugu poison.
The suspect?
The suspect found at the scene
has been dead for three months.
A 3-month-old corpse committed murder?
Sir.
What a crazy case we've got here.
Again.
THE CURSED: DEAD MAN'S PREY
Hello, Current Affairs listeners.
Today's guest is
the author of "Hatred and Sorcery"
and co-CEO of the
independent news
channel Urban Detective.
CEO or Author?
Which do you prefer?
Call me a journalist.
That's my main job.
Journalist Lim Jin-hee, it is.
As a journalist, you were criticized
for believing in superstitions
and you wanted to tell your side
of the story
through this controversial book.
So! It's about the ancient black magic
and casting curses, correct?
Yes, the ancient form of sorcery is...
Hold on, the listeners are posting
a lot of comments already.
Have you had any
contact with the sorcerer
who went missing?
No, not yet.
That leaves you without
your strongest witness to back you up.
That's unfortunate.
I hope the sorcerer is
listening and gets in touch.
Right! Let's go to our callers.
Already?
Yes! Hello?
Hello?
Hello.
Who's this calling?
Reveal yourself!
There's no need to know.
Ms. Lim, there was a
weird case of a corpse
murdering someone last night.
Check with the police.
You'll see I'm telling the truth.
Uh, excuse me, but...
Shut up.
I'm talking to Lim Jin-hee.
Excuse me, but I'm the host here.
Cut it. What complete nonsense…
Hold on.
Go on.
I am the murderer.
I want you to interview me
live at 2PM tomorrow
I just sent you the address.
I'd like a lot of people to watch it.
Until then.
Um, everyone?
We'll be back after the commercials.
Hey! What the hell was that?
URBAN DETECTIVE
I'll call you back.
Where is Pil-sung?
Not important.
The press is going nuts
asking if that was real.
There are also a bunch of people
searching for keywords.
They said we faked it for the book.
How dare they!
Where is Pil-sung?
Upstairs. Just a sec.
Hey you, come here.
Our new video intern.
Hello. My name is Jessy Jeong.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too!
I've always wanted to be
a brave journalist like you.
Alright... I respect her, too.
Why do you still have your bag?
- Good to meet you.
- Good luck!
Did you hire an intern?
I see you've met Jessy.
She's got no experience
so salary negotiation went well.
And she's not from here.
Did you look into the
case from the radio?
The documents are there.
The victim?
Kim Jung-kyun. 46.
Seungil Pharmaceuticals researcher
divorced 4 years ago…
Seungil Pharmaceuticals?
It's poisoning.
There were bite marks.
The suspect's photo is on the back.
Autopsy shows
he's been dead for three months.
What?
Just like what he said.
A corpse killed someone.
The suspect's identity?
Police don't know yet
I have to look into it.
Strange tattoo.
Isn't that like a stigmata?
No.
Okay.
It does look like some sigil.
I'll ask Professor Tak.
- I've already asked Tak!
- Good morning.
- Hi, honey!
- Give it to me.
What brings you here?
Is it our anniversary?
Making jokes now, are we?
Jung!
Congratulations on moving
to regional investigations.
Now you get more time
with your wife.
I moved over a year ago.
How did you get this case file
that hasn't been announced yet?
Jung-hoon, this hasn't
been made public?
- Was it you again?
- Sorry, sir.
Why are you here anyway?
Don't do the interview tomorrow.
Why,
because you can't stand
seeing your wife do well?
Come on, it's her first
scoop after setting up
the company.
We need to sell all these books
- to pay the rent.
- It's no ordinary case.
You could be put in danger again.
I know.
It's not an ordinary case.
Let's say the caller is the murderer.
Can he prove it?
What about motive?
What motive...
There's not even enough
evidence to indict.
Let's hear him out
before arresting him.
Right.
Okay, fine.
Let's hear what he says.
But! Police will be on standby,
okay?
Fine.
Jin-hee, do you hear me?
Yes...
I'll do as you say, don't worry.
Aren't you worried?
Nope, not when I have
such a great husband.
Bye.
What do I do with the books?
Leave them downstairs.
Pil-sung, ID that corpse
as soon as possible.
Jin-hee.
My junior working for
an occult magazine
sent me this. Take a look.
It's a ritual at a haunted
house in Shikoku, Japan.
Check out the shaman.
MYSTERY GIRL, APPEARING
WITH THE EXORCIST
So-jin?
It's her, right?
Apparently she worked
with a Japanese shaman
then disappeared again.
If we find So-jin
people will believe you
and the books will fly off the shelves.
Can I call you sis?
- I am a sorcerer.
- A sorcerer?
He is a demon.
This is a spiritual battle.
If you have his photo, name in Chinese
and something of
his, I can cast a spell.
Joo, to pour, and hwan for joy!
Let's cast a spell.
Die…
Die!
Feeling guilty about cursing a scumbag?
You are a good person.
Sis, I will hold onto
this demon forever.
So-jin! No!
So-jin!
Die!
Jin-hee.
Remember, cut off the broadcast
if you feel something is off.
Will he show up?
We got over 20,000 people watching.
If this falls through
we'll lose all our ads.
Don't worry.
He's coming.
Don't worry, okay?
No need to worry.
You, hands out of pockets.
Sir, someone's going in.
Bucket hat, grey jacket.
Blackish pants
man in mid-40s.
Check. Everyone focus!
Yes sir. Check.
Copy that.
He's heading to the interview room.
Looks like he's our guy.
Jin-hee… A man is heading your way.
Are you here for the interview?
Go right ahead.
Hello. I'm Lim Jin-hee.
Let me just put a mic on you.
Why is she so slow.
Damn it.
I'll do it.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
URBAN DETECTIVE
I'm Lim Jin-hee of Urban Detective.
We're here in a live interview
with the man who claims to be behind
the corpse murder case.
May I ask your name?
Park Yong-ho.
Okay, Mr. Park.
Is that your real name?
Want my social security number?
770303 - 10222159.
No criminal record.
But he's reported missing.
I am a sorcerer who
can control corpses.
I made a dead body
commit that murder from 2 days ago.
Using a corpse to commit murder.
That's quite hard to believe.
You will believe me soon.
Sorry?
Right… let's get to that later.
First, can you tell me
why you asked for an interview?
To warn.
I will commit three more murders.
First, two days from now at 2PM.
I will kill Seungil Pharmaceuticals'
director, Kim Min-sub.
And two days after that at 2PM
I'll kill their exec
director, Lee Sang-in.
In another two days at 2PM
I'll kill their chairman,
Byun Seung-il.
Preventing the murders is simple.
The chairman has to offer
a sincere apology in an
exclusive interview with you.
Any other methods won't count.
The chairman must apologize in person.
Ms. Lim, you'll judge if
that apology is sincere
and show it to the world.
And... this interview is now over.
I'm getting out of here.
Situation alert! Block all exits!
Drop the knife, Mr. Park Yong-ho.
Mr. Park, please put the knife down.
This is all part of the process.
Damn it, what are you doing?!
- The broadcast has to continue.
- Hey!
80,000 viewers.
Park, stop right there.
Mr. Park.
If I get hurt
who will interview the chairman?
The stairs!
Stop it!
Please stop, Mr. Park.
Where are they?
Keep rolling!
Drop your weapon! You are surrounded!
Drop the knife!
Stop! Park!
I will shoot if you move.
Drop the knife!
Drop it!
- Over there!
- Sir!
Mr. Park.
Why did you choose me?
You have to
figure that out for yourself.
Jin-hee!
The chairman must apologize in person
or Kim Min-sub, Lee
Sang-in, Byun Seung-il
will all die.
Drop it! Stop!
Drop the knife!
Does the chairman know about this?
You know he is resting
at his summer house
because of diabetes.
We don't have to tell him
until we have assessed the situation.
Assess what, Byun?
If that lunatic is serious
I'll die if the chairman
doesn't apologize.
Mr. Lee, please say something!
You're next after me.
Calm down, will you? Mr. Kim.
You know full well the company
is working on a billion dollar deal
with SFD now.
That lunatic, Park Yong-ho.
He used to work in our lab.
Zip it, Mr. Kim!
The shareholders
have been calling all day
to check if we use harmful ingredients.
That video will be
pulled off the internet.
Ms. Byun sure knows
how to handle things.
You panic over some madman's threat
and tell the chairman to apologize?
Have you no shame?
What? Hey!
I've been serving the chairman
for nearly 30 years!
How dare you talk to me like that?
Pack it in.
Okay, fine.
The police is on the case.
And we'll handle Mr. Kim's security.
Let's call it a day.
It's okay, man. Get some rest.
Managing Director Byun Mi-young.
I thought I recognized you.
You're the heir
to Seungil Pharmaceuticals?
There's a ridiculous rumour like that?
When Mr. Lee is right here.
You saw the video?
I heard Park worked here.
Yes, he headed the new
medicine research lab
I looked into it.
He suddenly disappeared
and caused a lot of trouble.
His family reported him
missing two months ago.
He was working late
and didn't come home.
Can we check the security
cam footage from that day?
That might be difficult.
It was in our old building
which is closed down.
I'm more curious
about how the police
is looking at the case.
Controlling a corpse?
As if that makes sense.
Right. It doesn't make sense.
What I'm really curious
about, Ms. Byun,
is why Park
is demanding a public apology.
- Who knows.
- Our audit team will look into it
I am concerned for my father
but Mr. Lee and Mr. Kim
are like uncles to me.
I looked into it.
A corpse controlled by a sorcerer.
We call it "Jaechaui".
By the way, I forgot to tell you.
I've got tenure.
Congratulations. Let's get started.
Right.
According to the ancient Book of Tales.
Jaechaui is a reanimated corpse.
They spoke
and were intelligent like people.
During the Goryeo Kingdom, Minister Han
imitated reanimated corpses
by painting his hands black
as a joke
and sang a requiem
saying 'I am here!'
That's right. Park's hands
and the suspect's
hand in the first case.
They were black, right?
Based on the evidences
the corpses were clearly
controlled by a sorcerer.
So, someone is controlling
the Jaechaui, the reanimated dead?
Yes! I did some research.
This pattern is only
used in one country,
Indonesia.
How can you be so sure?
This is Indonesian language.
Sorry... So, I translated it.
On the first corpse
it said 'The first revenge'
On Park's body from yesterday
it was written, 'Draw attention'.
Who would do this and why?
Dukun!
In Indonesia
there are shamans who
practice black magic.
Recently, an Indonesian politician
hired a dukun santet
to curse his opponent.
It was in the news, too.
Hold on.
Dukun santet.
Dukun can control a
corpse in many ways.
Mix soil from where the corpse died
with the blood of the dukun
to make a clay doll.
And cast a curse on it.
Park's face
crumbled like clay, right?
- Yes.
- That's right.
To gain control of the corpse
he makes an offering to the ghost.
Place the offering
and around here
place the doll with hair
or fingernail of the corpse
he wants to control.
Finally, write down the commands.
This is a contract of a sort.
Correct!
A contract with the
sorcerer's commands.
If a dukun is really doing this
he could use another dead body
to commit murder tomorrow.
I found out the ID of the corpse
that killed Kim Jung-kyun.
Who is it?
Hwang Jin-gook.
Reported missing by
his family five years ago.
He gave his personal information
to a gang making illegal bank accounts.
The gang collects
personal information from homeless.
Their boss is now in prison
for running an illegal gambling den.
Meet the broker and call me tomorrow.
Okay, got it.
Talk to you later.
Who's there?
Jessy.
What are you doing by yourself?
Just checking the gear for tomorrow.
Okay.
Oh, you did well yesterday.
Sorry?
You chased after Park
and filmed him until the end.
Thank you.
That sorcerer... is her name So-jin?
Huh?
You read my book.
Woo-chan said that
the sorcerer must be found
to clear your name
and help sell the book.
That's not really the reason.
Then what?
Well.
To her, I'm family.
I wanted to tell her through the book
that she can come back any time.
Do you have family, Jessy?
Dad and two younger brothers.
But dad doesn't care about us.
He never looked after us
only thinks about himself.
He wasn't there when mom died.
Sorry I've rambled on.
You must be busy.
No. We're a team now.
Let's talk more
when this case is over.
Okay.
Go home.
You got four years for running
an illegal gambling den.
That's rather long, isn't it?
Who are you again?
I was a police detective for 20 years
before I became a private detective.
I know many squad and section chiefs.
Answer my questions
and I could look into
reducing your time.
If you are interested.
What do you want to know?
You know the Seungil Pharm case?
The crazy case all over the TV now.
The suspect in the
first murder is a corpse
that's been dead three months.
When he was alive, he was a homeless
who sold personal information to you.
So what?
What did Seungil Pharm make you do?
As the time of pre-announced murder
is approaching
tensions are high
here at Seungil Pharm.
The police is treating
it as a terror threat
and placed two SWAT units
in the area.
Cut! I'll be right back.
Jin-hee, how's it going?
I missed you.
Do you have anything for me?
I don't know anything.
You shouldn't burn bridges
even if you're independent now.
Back then, we were competitors but...
No, we were her competitors.
You really don't know that guy
you interviewed?
Give me something!
What's with all the flies?
What the heck.
They were talking shit behind you
and now they want intel?
Let them be.
You know what it's like.
Sure.
Nothing unusual yet?
No.
Could anything happen
with all these police here?
We'll see.
Where's Jessy?
She's getting us coffee
and she is taking the whole day.
Such a scatterbrain.
You were way worse back then.
Don't bring up the past.
Be nice to her.
- She works hard.
- Yes, ma'am.
Sir, what brings you here?
I dropped by on the way somewhere
to help put the executives at ease.
Have some coffee.
The police will keep you safe.
So don't worry.
Thank you.
You saw that monster, too.
It looked just like human.
How can the police stop it?
Don't worry.
The SWAT team is here.
Yes, I'll tell them
to take special care.
Don't worry.
About six months ago,
Seungil Pharm quietly gathered
test subjects for a new medicine.
It paid well
with a 30 percent commission.
But for some reason
they only wanted homeless
or those with no families.
When we couldn't find any more homeless
we recruited illegal immigrants.
Illegal immigrants?
Stop.
No outsiders beyond this point.
Sir, you can't come here.
Situation alert!
Freeze!
Attack his leg!
Is he armed?
He is unarmed!
Then take him down!
Responding to call!
Squad 1 to rear entrance.
Squad 2 responding!
Whatever the test was
they all died within months.
How many did you recruit for them?
Let's see...
How many was it?
One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven,
eight, nine
ten.
Ten people?
No. Ten groups of ten.
A hundred?
- Woo-chan.
- Yes.
What the…?
Camera, hurry!
Film it!
Defensive formation! Hurry.
Kim!
Defensive line is breached!
They're all monsters!
Kill them!
But they don't appear armed.
I don't care. Shoot them!
We are in position.
Do we open fire?
Do we fire? Sir!
Aim for the legs.
Sir, the guns are useless!
They are going up the stairs.
Stairs… block them.
Block the stairs!
We need to get out of here
before they get to us.
Min-sub, let's go. Now!
Kill the lights and lead the way.
To the underground parking lot.
Yes, sir.
Halt!
Go left.
Straight, and left to
the emergency elevator.
Activating elevator.
Be as quick as possible.
Woo-chan, follow me.
What? Where are you going?
Sung-joon! Are you okay?
Jin-hee.
Get out of the way!
Move!
Hold on tight.
Wait...
Sir!
We're going to the police agency.
Hi!
What? Hey!
What the...?!
My kids and wife
are studying abroad now.
I miss them.
170,000 viewers and counting.
That's them.
Film the taxis.
Yes.
Left!
Over there, look out!
No!
Go away! Stop!
Hit the brake!
Keep rolling!
Got it!
Oh, God! No!
Please help me!
Let go!
Sung-joon.
Wake up... Please!
Ambulance!
You...!
I'm sorry.
Where were you?
And why didn't you pick up?
You got me worried sick.
Do you even know what happened?
Never mind. What's the point...
The PSP toxin
is spreading rapidly.
All patients are critically ill.
It's shocking as no
treatment has worked
for what we've done so far.
But we'll do our best.
Why are you standing there? Sit.
This was a gift from the South Africa
for sending free vaccines.
Sir, Director Kim is dead.
I know. I saw the news too.
The researcher and Min-sub
had the same cause of death.
That's fine. You can tell me.
Seung-il.
They both died
from the PSP toxin.
It's clearly linked
to the clinical trial.
But we had no choice.
You must apologize.
To whom?
To the people
that took part in the trial!
But they're all dead.
Apologize to corpses?
Did you even think about apologizing?
I would've apologized if
this was a personal matter.
But I am the chairman
and it's a corporate issue.
Sir!
I'll discuss it with Mi-young.
You'll discuss it with your daughter?
Our time has passed.
We need to support the
company's new leader.
I'll be off, Mr. Chairman.
Sang-in.
Uncle, leaving so soon?
I feel bad seeing you like that.
You should've stayed away from Min-sub.
Take it. It's raining hard.
You spearheaded those trials.
What do you mean?
But father and all of you had approved.
No matter what.
We've been making
medicine to save lives
but you pushed ahead
with the trials for money.
You feel no responsibility?
Uncle, it was all for the company.
You devoted your life to it.
Stick it to the end.
This isn't what your
father and I dreamed of.
We must at least...
Why would you have
dreams for my company?
What?
No wonder the blackmailer
sees us as pushovers.
All old and soft...
So, you will be leading Seungil Pharm?
Okay.
Please give me some time
until the strategy
team and I make plans.
The movement of the
corpses that attacked Seungil
was clumsy.
Perhaps too many bodies
were being controlled
at the same time.
And the mark they had...
The one on the wrist.
One of them had their wrist blown off
and couldn't move.
The mark must be the link
that connects the bodies to the dukun.
Professor, what do
you think about Jung?
They can't do much at the hospital.
It's not so much of the toxin
but a curse that was cast upon him.
Then, the solution is...
For whoever cursed him to lift it or...
Kill the bastard that cursed him.
Well... sure.
Thank you.
We'll call if we have more questions.
Any time. Good luck.
Let's summarize.
Seungil Pharm recruited
100 homeless for a clinical trial.
To avoid backlash if
anything goes wrong.
There weren't enough homeless
so they recruited
illegal immigrants too.
And there were Indonesians among them.
Right.
All of the participants
died from side effect.
Park Yong-ho was given the job
to take care of the 100 bodies.
But he'd been dead for two months
when he had the interview.
Hyun told me this.
They all died and
about a month later
a Southeast Asian
man came to my office.
Southeast Asia?
He had a family who got a job
at Seungil for great money
but he lost touch with his family
after that letter.
Who was his family?
No idea.
I just gave him
- the phone number of...
- Park Yong-ho.
Yeah, the guy that did the interview.
I told him to go talk to him.
Do you remember what he looked like?
He was dressed like... a shaman.
A little creepy.
A dukun.
And when Park vanished
so did the 100 bodies.
The dukun kills Park
and reanimates the body
uses him to move the bodies
and make 100 walking corpses.
Is there any way to
identify this dukun?
We need the name
list of test participants
to find the dukun's family.
How do we get the list out of Seungil?
Get the camera ready for an interview.
Now? What interview?
URBAN DETECTIVE: A VOICE FOR THE WEAK.
The project began when
SFD proposed developing
a base material for a chemical weapon
using shellfish toxins.
So homeless and illegal
immigrants were recruited
as test subjects.
To avoid any legal issues.
It's not because you thought
they wouldn't create any issues.
It's because they are
poor and powerless.
Yes, I guess so.
The people the murderer wants to kill
are those who approved the trials.
Were there any Indonesians
among the test participants?
I don't know the details
but we can check their applications
from the files I brought.
This interview will be
used as indicting evidence.
You knew from the start
that this clinical trial was illegal.
Any trial can have side effects.
And sacrificing a few can save many.
What was this trial for?
Sacrificing a few
to help kill tens of thousands?
I offered my apology
and I'll pay the price in my own way.
What about the chairman?
Will he apologize?
Our chairman?
He will never apologize.
That's the kind of man he is.
Your company killed innocent people.
Many officers got injured
while protecting you
and they're dying right now!
I heard about your husband.
I'm truly sorry.
There is a list of participants
but the information is sparse.
It's not enough to
find the dukun's family.
Maybe I'll crosscheck
with immigration data.
Just where on earth is this dukun?
Wherever he is
he must be with the bodies.
Dukun, casting curses.
Mixes his bloods with soil
to make a clay doll.
Soil from where the corpse died.
Where the corpse died…
Soil.
In order to make a walking corpse
you gotta make a doll
using the soil from
where they died, right?
That's right.
The test subjects
died at the lab.
It was a temporary
lab in their old building.
Is this it?
Seungil Pharm's old building.
The address is right.
The dukun could be there.
I'll go.
I'll try to find his family.
I'll go with you, Jin-hee.
I'll send Tak the address.
- To the immigration office?
- Yes.
- Young-su, you go with him.
- Yes sir.
Hurry.
All of these?
I think we're here.
That's gotta be it.
Pull over.
You okay?
What's all this?
Let's ask Tak about it later.
Let's go up first.
Jin-hee!
This way!
Run!
You okay?
I'm fine.
This way.
So-jin.
We have to go now.
Detective Yoo!
Jin-hee!
Hurry!
Go on ahead!
Detective Yoo!
Detective Yoo! Quickly!
Come on.
No, not yet!
Right wrist, that's their weakness.
Jin-hee.
Welcome back, So-jin.
Welcome back.
I travelled everywhere
to stop the evil spirit in me.
I spent one and a half year in Japan.
Then I went to a temple in China.
I couldn't find a
way to stop the spirit
but learned about my body
and sorceries that use the evil spirit.
I wanted to stay there
and avoid people
for as long as I could.
Then I connected to your dream
and knew something was wrong.
So-jin.
Don't go off on your own again.
Never.
Jin-hee.
Lee Sang-in committed suicide.
What?
Hello? Speaking.
Couldn't he just die at home?
Father, it's me.
Hi, Woo-chan.
Seungil Pharm just called.
The chairman wants to apologize
in an exclusive interview with you.
What?
After Lee ended up like that
maybe he's afraid he's next?
Woo-chan, prepare the filming equipment
and go to Seungil now.
I'll be right over.
Okay.
Please wrap up with
Prof. Tak when he arrives.
Okay.
Let's go, So-jin.
I'll stay and look around.
I think the dukun is here.
But So-jin...
To lift the curse off Sung-joon
we need to get the dukun.
Alright but...
Nothing dangerous, okay?
Be careful.
Will we find anything
by going through these documents?
What's going to happen to Jung?
Do you know my motto? God...
'God protects the righteous', right?
I've heard it so much
that I memorized it.
Do you know anyone
more righteous than him?
God will protect him.
Yes sir.
She's here.
This way.
You must be the journalist?
All this media attention must be
doing you some good.
Okay, we're ready.
Excuse me.
I tried to come quickly.
But got delayed at the rest stop.
It's a rare opportunity for an academic
to encounter such a powerful dukun.
I'm so nervous!
- He better still be here.
- Yeah.
Please take a look at this.
This is no ordinary pattern.
It's completely different to
talismans that banish ghosts
or bring luck.
It's a spiritual chamber
that conceals things.
Conceals things?
Like what I was doing earlier.
It conceals the
presence of what's there.
That's right. This says 'exist not'
So, if you delete
'Tidak' from 'Tidak ada'…
No! You can't do that!
You're left with 'ada' meaning 'exist'.
Dear citizens.
I ran this company for 30 years
with only the public's health in mind.
But recent events have caused concern
and I apologize to the people for that.
We will endeavor to become
a more responsible company.
Thank you.
The suspect didn't ask you
to apologize to the public.
Then, apologize to whom?
To the victims, of course.
The company killed 100
people in an illegal test
and hid that fact.
It's the victims and their
families you owe it to.
Like I said, I don't
really know about that.
But if he wants an apology.
So I should apologize, right?
I apologize.
I apologize to the
victims of the trial.
It was my fault.
I sincerely apologize to those
who cannot rest even in death.
Thank you.
Would that do?
No. I won't air that insincere apology.
Who are you to judge that?
Just put in on the internet.
If you don't apologize sincerely
the curse will not be lifted.
Did you not hear me?
A curse?
Oh, you're the crazy reporter
who got sacked for that crap.
Let's call it quits.
What?
The curse will kill your father, too.
We're getting out of here.
Mi-young, let's just do it.
What's this place?
Looks like a morgue.
Watch the floor.
It's a spiritual chamber.
This is why he asked for Jin-hee.
No…
Ms. Lim.
Does his apology sound sincere?
My daughter
did everything to support her family.
Because of my useless abilities
she would commit to anything.
But you…
can't even apologize right?
Jessy, no!
Jin-hee!
Protect the chairman!
Father, this way.
This way, sir.
- Woo-chan.
- Yes.
Get the gear.
- Now!
- I'm on it.
So-jin...
Hang in there, So-jin!
Cover the back.
Quick!
This way… hurry!
Get inside. I'll stop the monster.
But this is Lee's office.
Hurry! Father!
It feels wrong…
Come on! Stop her!
Yes, ma'am. Get her!
I'm sorry...
Please spare me.
Don't kill me.
Please!
So-jin!
Father, are you okay?
Where have you been?
Lee gave everything to the police.
Everyone involved must go
for the company to survive.
You all worked so hard to get us here.
Your generation must go
for a new world to begin.
Thank you for everything, dad.
Take my sins with you, and rest.
Are you alright?
Father! Please…
Father!
Calm down, and take a seat.
Jin-hee, are you okay?
Father…
Drop the act, Ms. Byun.
The mastermind has confessed.
Everything is on tape.
That won't be admissible in court.
Recordings can be manipulated.
You think I'll go down like this?
What did she do to her father?
She told him to take her sins…
and die?
Look at these comments.
Looks like you've been livestreamed.
How dare you...
Let's go to the station.
Don't touch me!
Justice is served once again?
Our role ends here.
Let's go, So-jin.
Don't feel guilty.
Tak said so too,
that the dukun was probably
going to offer himself.
I know.
It seemed the target
of his final revenge
wasn't the chairman but himself.
When I connected with him.
Atin.
Dad!
I made mommy a seashell necklace
and she thanked me with a kiss.
He told me not to focus
on the evil inside like he did
and lose the people I love.
UHM Ji Won
JEONG Ji So
Directed by KIM Yong Wan
3 MONTHS LATER
Byun Mi-young,
Seungil's next chairperson
was acquitted on lack of evidence.
So what? Give me my keys.
Can't you apologize sincerely
and be judged by law?
Why would I?
What are you gonna do about it?
Something of hers,
a photo,
and name in Chinese.
We don't want to do this either.
THE CURSED: DEAD MAN'S PREY
Why is there so little?
You can't work properly
you say crazy shit all day.
Get him out of here!
Come on, man.
- Hey, out…
- Why? Let go!
- What do you mean why? Get out!
- Hey, hold on!
Show your face again
and I'll kill you!
Those damned demons…
Master!